Daisy Lin

zichun.l@gmail.com 0423274617



Hospitality professional with 6+ years' experience looking to apply knowledge and skills to a brand-new career journey.

Process-driven to ensure consistent, positive customer and business outcomes. Excited to be challenged and succeed in a new environment.

SKILLS

- Process management
- Customer Service
- Team Work
- Fast-Learner

- Resilience
- Critical Thinking

EXPERIENCE

Demi Chef (Functions/events)

Delaware North, Melbourne - July 2023 - Present

- Supporting the day-to-day production operation across event-day and non-event day catering while maintaining food safety standards during high volume food preparation
- Requisitioning the appropriate amount of food product in accordance with the established policies and procedures, and practice the established occupational health and safety guidelines (OH&S)

Pastry Chef

Lune Croissanterie, Fitzroy - Jan 2022 - June 2023

- Responsible for day-to-day operations across multiple sections within the kitchen
- Production planning within capacity forecasts
- Monitoring quality and supply of all stock and communicating any issues with managers or suppliers
- Training of new chefs

Store Manager

Miss China, South Melbourne - June 2020 - December 2021

- Workforce planning and coordination of daily business operations
- Induction and training of new team members and continual upskilling of current team
- Delivering a superior product and maximizing customer satisfaction
- Building professional relationships with suppliers by managing and forecasting stock levels

Demi Chef (Pan/Hot entrée)

Prince of York, Sydney - July 2019 - March 2020

Responsible for the pan section of the kitchen, prepping meat, filleting fish, making fresh pasta on a daily basis whilst ensuring food quality and taste is of the highest standard

Commis Chef (Cold Larder/Pastry)

Regatta Rosebay, Sydney - April 2018 - June 2019

Responsible for operating the larder section of the kitchen, preparing ingredients, running daily food service, and monitoring stock levels



EDUCATION

Diploma of Hospitality ManagementQuality Training and Hospitality College

Graduated September 2019

Certificate IV in Commercial Cookery

Quality Training and Hospitality College Graduated January 2019 **B.A Music Performance - Major: Cello**Tainan Nation University of the Arts
Graduated June 2015